### NOAH FIGUERAS RAMIREZ



noahfigueras@gmail.com

+1 424 413 7839

in linkedin.com/in/noahfigueras/

### **SUMMARY**

Currently studying a BA in Computer Science with 2+ years of experience in Business Administration and additional knowledge of running my own company. I moved to the US seeking to develop my skills and work in the technology and surfing industry (I am a Green Card resident holder), but the beginnings are always tough, so I am first looking for an entry job to get settled in San Diego for the first months. I define myself as a self-learner and dedicated worker aiming to help achieve company goals and take on more responsibility as I get deeper into my professional career.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Universitat Oberta Catalunya, Barcelona, Spain

September 2017 – Present

Bachelor of Computer Science

# Mondragon University, Barcelona, Spain

September 2014 – June

2017

Bachelor in Business Administration, Leadership and Entrepreneurship & Innovation

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Rafa Nadal Academy, Mallorca, Spain

June 2018 - September

2018

Water Activities Monitor

- Teach surf from 8 to 18-year-old kids.
- Responsible for up to 150 kids per week.

### Educatennis, Barcelona, Spain

February 2018 – Present

Website Designer and Developer

• Back & front end development (Web app in development)

## Abacus Cooperativa, Barcelona, Spain

September 2017 – January 2018

Store Keeper

• In charge of ordering the store, replenish stock and assist to customers.

### Initi Company, Barcelona, Spain

September 2015 – June 2017

Co-Founder

- Started a company to launch and develop university projects initicompany.com
- Used this platform to launch and develop Fancy Fences

### Fancy Fences, Barcelona, Spain

September 2015 – June 2017

Founder

• Developed a project to promote street art in the city of Barcelona – fancyfences.com

#### ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Languages: Spanish, Catalan, English, and German.
- Surf instructor Certificate Level I Spanish Surfing Federation.
- Leadership, Team management, Hard working, Sales.
- Programming Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Eis, REST, Node.is, C, Python and Linux Distributions.